It's high time I chromed up.
Get the fuck outta here.
I already gave you the quote to sell.
Not here to sell.
I'm here to install.
Listen. That's military grade.
You either got the build
to handle it or you don't.
And choom, you don't got it.
Spoken like a ripper
who cares about his clients.
Hah! Snarky for a kid
who can't even afford me.
Fuck you.
Hold on.
Fuck it, man. I'll bite.
I'll chip you up.
But when you come crying to yank it off…
'cause it's poaching your brain,
I get the Sandy for free.
So, ready to rip?
At the convention, Lavabre attempted
to persuade Arasaka by using the…
Martinez, David.
Your tardiness has been recorded.
Get a load of this guy…
Is he serio--
We're at school you gonk!
There are cameras. Have you lost your--
Afraid of getting caught?
'Cause I sure ain't.
Come on.
Well?
Ow… That hurt…
Ow… What did you do?!
What kind of implant is that?
You broke my nose!
You're done for!
My father's an Arasaka exec!
On the Academy's board!
Do you know how easy it'd be
to have you expelled?
Like I give a shit.
Is he serio--
My father's an Arasaka exec!
On the Academy's board!
Do you know how easy it'd be
to have you expelled?
Marcus, why am I being shown footage
of my own son being assaulted?
This student is David Martinez,
17 years old, from Santo Domingo.
He is a top student at the Academy,
but he was found using a bootleg wreath
that corrupted the Academy's hardware.
He has no father and his mother was
recently killed in a traffic accident.
He owes a considerable amount of debt--
How is this relevant?
Notice his movements…
He has the Sandevistan that James Norris
had at the time of this death.
The case that was filed
as a cyberpsychotic incident.
Yes, sir.
Yet, unlike the soldier, this student
displays no side effects from the implant.
His tolerance for cybernetics could make
him a prime candidate to test the product.
I see. And where is he now?
He was expelled, sir.
Summon him.
Lure him with the promise of
financial aid if you must.
And what of your son?
As my heir, it's high time he learned…
what it means to serve
the company's best interests.
I'm so fucked.
Wash cycle complete…
Come with me.
The hell is your problem?
What?
You're messing with my work.
Work? Looked more like a picksocket to me.
You some kinda badge?
Can't believe you're a petty thief…
Do I know you?
No… not really. Just--
Ooh, you're in trouble.
Huh?
Really? A Sandevistan?
Not an off-the-rack model, either.
I won't press you.
This is Night City after all…
Crazy idea. How about we work together?
What, stealing?
I only steal from Arasaka suits.
What about me then? I look corpo to you?
My scan picked up an ID
from Arasaka Academy.
But you're right,
you definitely don't look the type.
I dropped out.
Oh? A bad boy.
It's just 'Saka you target?
You in?
Gonna break poor momma's heart, y'know.
Lesson number one.
Less judgment, more awareness.
Yeah, yeah. So, what's my cut?
We'll split the haul 80-20.
Fuck that. Don't you need my Sandevistan?
But I'm the one pushing
the klepped shards.
Plus, now I have a trainee to supervise.
Trainee…?
I'm actually tight on eddies right now.
Can't we do 60-40?
70-30. And I'll pay you
the second the job's done.
Fine.
It's a deal.
Call me Lucy.
David.
So? How did I do?
I'd say you're well worth the 20%.
It's 30!
Kidding.
Keep it rolling on another car?
Maybe a different line.
By now, someone's probably noticed.
We should keep the risk to a minimum…
How bad?
Rookie mistake.
Hasn't taken any precautions
since installing that implant.
Which immunosuppressant is he on?
He insured?
No clue. Doesn't look like he would be.
Any family or guardian? Anyone I can call?
Dunno. Parents, I guess.
He used to go to the Academy.
Arasaka? No wonder he could afford this.
Hold on…
Hey. How ya feeling?
I'm gonna be sick…
Which immunosuppressant do you take?
Immuno… what?
Wow, man…
You're psycho.
Hey, we passed the…
Oh my.
Listen, choom, the kid's got
an implant that'll fetch a nice price.
Just sit back, relax and--
What? You cut a deal
with the Scavengers or something?
Sit back or I'll take your chrome, too.
Sorry, David.
Looks like your cut's down to 20.
Let's go!
Whoops.
Hey, not dying, are ya?
Doc…
Huh?
Doc's clinic… Please… take…
David, buddy…
You look like shit.
Thanks…
How many times you use it?
Six… No, eight?
Jesus Henry Christ!
A grown-ass man
couldn't take that punishment.
I was fine…
But then my nose popped a cork.
This gonk didn't know about
immunosuppressants.
Didn't see the need.
Of course you didn't.
Just sell him the meds.
Shit off the shelf's not gonna cut it.
It'll cost ya.
You good for it?
You charging me?
Fucking right I am!
Ain't running no charity.
How much'll these buy?
Two days' worth.
That's it?
Plenty of other rippers out there.
Of course, that might land you
back with the Scavs.
Greedy bastard…
You really don't want it gone?
Nope.
Still can't believe it…
Eight times in one goddamn day.
You're either a total masochist or…
Listen. Don't use it more than
two times a day. Three max.
Even if your body can take it,
that egghead of yours can't.
Your brain's gonna get scrambled.
A single implant
could make me a cyberpsycho?
Never heard anything like that before.
Goes to show you…
just how dangerous that thing is.
All done?
Yeah.
Guess that's a wrap for today.
I can keep going.
No way, I'm not babysitting a cyberpsycho.
Only use the Sandevistan
when you really need to.
Lots of other ways to churn out eds.
Still willing to work with me
after all that?
Think I'd let you go
without being paid back first?
Well, good. I need the eddies.
That's the spirit.
Sure you're not up for more tonight?
I'm kinda lagging on rent.
No more today. Quit asking.
Okay…
Come with me.
I knew you wanted to!
Not work-related.
Huh?
Right here.
You, uh… live alone?
Yeah?
Huh.
Wait, are you nervous?
No.
Your first time?
Hey, fuck off!
Take a seat.
I've only got beer. You drink?
Uh, yeah.
Cheers.
Seriously? You've never drunk before?
No, I have. It's just…
I don't like carbonated drinks or smokes.
Do people like that really exist?
I'm not lying.
Sure you aren't.
And what's up with that getup anyway?
Take it off.
What? Why?
Just do it. Come on.
H-Hey!
Don't mess with that…
Edgerunners?
It's another word for cyberpunk.
It's who you wanna be, right?
I'm actually a fan of JK's
"EDGERUNNERS" series.
You serious?
Look who's talking.
What's up with that tacky poster?
You got a problem?
Uh… no problem.
Just always whacked me how those ads
make it seem like some kind of paradise.
I mean, lots of peeps died trying to
turn that dumb rock into something useful.
Sounds more like a prison than paradise.
Sounds like someone did their homework.
The Academy teaches you things
they don't show in the ads.
As expected of a preppy Academy boy.
It's not like that.
Isn't it? Never caught a pleb
attending a 'Saka school.
It's not!
My mom and I, we weren't well off.
The Academy normally
wouldn't have taken me.
But my mom had to work real
damn hard to keep me in.
You wanna know the kicker though?
I knew from day one that I'd never belong.
Then why did you stick around for so long?
Good fucking question. Guess it's 'cause
Mom wanted me to get a 'Saka job,
climb the corporate ladder…
That was her wish… Or dream, I guess.
That's why.
That's not your dream, though.
Not my dream?
Well, yeah. You and your mom
are two different people.
Why should you need to work for her dream?
There's nothing wrong with that.
You have to find your own dream.
Sounds like you've found yours.
You're joking.
You called it a prison, but to me,
this city is a whole lot worse.
Here?
I just wanna go away as far as possible.
Lemme show you something.
Whoa! Check the resolution on this!
I can feel the fucking sun!
It connects through your personal link
to let you feel the sun's heat.
Of course, you'd burn to a crisp
if it was the real temperature,
so I made sure to tweak it down.
Want me to change it back?
No, this is fun!
You look ridiculous!
Pretty cool, huh?
This is amazing!
Isn't it?
Over here.
First time I've ever shown anyone this.
Oh… really?
So, like… why me?
No idea. Guess it just felt right.
You know…
I think we'd make a good team.
Yeah…
Huh?
Hate to break it to ya,
but that implant belongs to me.
I'll be taking it back now.